Ho Trong Tin

Date of birth September, 1990

Gender Male

Phone 090 889 8558

Email toto1194@gmail.com

Address District Go Vap, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam



CAREER OBJECTIVE

Become a Professional Developer.

Update new technicals everyday and create good products for company and customers.

Training and support the new members.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2014 FPT APTECH ACADEMY

Software Engineer

CERTIFICATIONS

2014 Higher Diploma Degree in Computer Science

PERSONAL PROFILE & SKILLS

1 year of experience in software development as a C# Developer.

Technical skills:

- C# ASP.NET
- Entity framework
- SQL Server Database
- OOP Programming

Experience in solving technical issues, document issues.

Experience in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap.

Happy to research and training with new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2012 - 2013	AISOFT Software Company Software Engineer
	- Develope the PHP websites for Japanese customers.
	- Create, maintain the administrator website.
2015 - 2016	Operating room Retail System of FPT SHOP Software Engineer
	- Develope and design the C# promotion websites.
	- Create, maintain the administrator websites.
	- Maintain database of system.
2016 - now	FUTA TAXI Corporation Company Insurrance Staff, Software administrator - Manage the accident insurrances
	- Administrate navigation website GPS